http://www.build-your-website.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
We takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what
personal information we collect and how we use it.
Routine Information Collection
All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, time stamps and referring pages.
None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site.
The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Where necessary, Build-your-website uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.
Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information.
Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.
In particular this site use Google Adsense and,
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
You can find out about Google privacy policies and control your ad settings here.
Controlling Your Privacy
Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns.
Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.
Email Addresses
Our site’s registration and contact forms require that you enter your email address and contact name and other such information. This information is used to send out our electronic newsletter, query responses and other information about other products and services offered by the website www.build-your-website.co.uk.
We will not give away or sell your email address.
In the event that this website is sold you will be given 1 month advance notice and the option to remove yourself from the email list.
You are free to opt out of the list at any time!
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information.
If you have submitted personal  information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please click on this link and/or use our Contact Us page.
Updates and Effective Date
(www.Build-your-website.co.uk) reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree to (www.Build-your-website.co.uk‘s) Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.
Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
Contact Information
Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to
the webmaster by using the contact form.
Affiliate Programs
www.build-your-website.co.uk uses affiliate programs for monetization, which means when you click on links to various merchant sites that I recommend in my articles and make a purchase, this can result in a commission that is credited to this site.
Affiliations include, but are not limited to, Commission Junction, SiteSell, Amazon.com, Bluehost and 1and1 Hosting.
I only recommend products that I use, have used or have thoroughly researched. I do not do any paid reviews.
www.build-your-website.co.uk and the owner assume no liability for products purchased outside of www.build-your-website.co.uk.
Third-Party & Sponsor Ads
Google Adsense is also used for monetization. Ads appear in various locations and they are labeled with “Ads by Google”. www.build-your-website.co.uk does not personally endorse the products and services advertised in these ads.
These companies are not affiliated with www.build-your-website.co.uk. The only affiliation present is the one between www.build-your-website.co.uk and Google. In other words, commissions/profits are generated from Google for displaying these ads.
If you have questions about any affiliations on this website, please don’t hesitate to contact me. I’ll be more than happy to clarify or provide additional details if necessary.
www.build-your-website.co.uk  assumes no liability for products purchased from third-party websites or sponsor ads. Please make sure you read the terms and conditions of any product you purchase.
Polls
Are you more Interested in Learning More About
Technical e.g. HTML,Scripting etc
Non Technical e.g. Hosting,domain names etc
Promotion e.g. SEO
WordPress
Website Maintenance
Ecommerce
Loading ...
Ecommerce (4)
Hosting (10)
SEO (7)
Webmaster (15)
WordPress (35)
wordpress-coding (11)
Sitemap
|About & Contact | Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2004-2020 Build Your Website
By Steve Cope
